For boarding students at Bodwell, there is much more to consider
與一般中學生相比，博域中學的寄宿生
throughout the day than an average high school student
每天有更多事情需要考慮。
Students here are expected to responsibilities in all area their life
這裏的同學需要負起自己生活的方方面面的責任，
while adapting to a new environment, new school, and new people.
同時還要兼顧適應新環境、新學校和新人事，
It can be very overwhelming.
這些都不容易應付。
For this reason, it is necessary to establish a routine that students can follow,
所以，同學們需要有規可循，
to help them structure their day and develop the proper time management skills needed
以幫助他們安排好一天的時間，學會適當的時間管理技巧，
to be successful in all areas of a boarding student's life
從而收獲完滿的寄宿生活。
A student's day begins with the wake-up call at 7 a.m.
學生一天的生活，從早上七點的叫醒聲中開始，
By 8:00, all the boarding areas are closed and students
八點鐘，宿舍關門，
are not allowed to re-enter until the end of the academic day.
同學們不能再回去，直至當天的課堂學習結束。
We want students to develop the habit of bringing everything they need from their home to class
這樣做是要求同學們，養成從家裏帶齊一切所需物品到課堂的習慣。
Breakfast is available from 7:25 to 8:15 every morning
早餐供應是每天早上七點二十五分到八點十五分。
Breakfast is an important meal and we encourage students to eat by extending meal time past boarding closure.
早餐很重要，所以，我們把用餐時間，延至宿舍關門之後，以鼓勵同學們吃早餐。
At 3:30 p.m. The school day ends and clubs begin. These run from 3:30 to 4:30
下午三點半，學校下課，興趣小組活動開始，直至四點半。
This is a great opportunity for students to work on
這是讓學生每週一次、或者兩次
an extracurricular activity for once,  sometimes twice a week
參加課外活動的良機。
From 5:30 dinner is available for all boarding students.
晚餐從五點半開始，供應給所有寄宿學生，
Our cafeteria stays open during supper for 45 minutes
餐廳開放用飯的時間，維持45分鐘。
Study-hall begins at 6:00 with small group tutoring for those requiring extra help
溫習室時間從六點開始，為有需要額外幫肋的同學，進行小組補習。
At 7, Junior study all begins and at 8:15 we have senior study hall, where all senior students attend.
七點鐘，低年級溫習室開始；八點十五分，高年級學生加入高年級溫習室。
The library also remains open through the evening.
圖書館也是維持整晚開放。
Every Wednesday each individual Hall meets for announcements
逢星期三，每個堂社都會聚會，發佈公告，
and to discuss issues and further develop life skills and community building.
討論問題，開發生活技能，以及共建社區。
Every hall meeting is run a little differently.
每一堂社的聚會形式都略有差異，
It allows each hall to develop an individual sense of community within the boarding program.
這讓各個堂社在寄宿計劃中，養成一種個別化的共同體的感覺。
After study hall snack is available in students of thirty minutes free time
溫習之後，同學有三十分鐘自由時間，期間有小吃供應，
to begin heading back to their halls for curfew.
然後，返回堂社，宵禁開始。
By 10:15 students are up in their boarding halls and begin their bedtime routines.
十時十五分，學生回到宿舍，開始上床前的準備，
We give students an hour for their bedtime routine.
他們有一小時做上床前準備。
This is a time for students to wash up,
包括: 洗澡、漱洗、
build a sense of community in their halls as well as relax and reflect before bed.
與舍友交流，以及睡前放鬆身心和自我反省等。
We have a student that goes around to do the curfew check to-
宵禁時間內，會有一位同學到處察看檢查，
We give them some volunteer hours for that.
他所用的時間，會算入他的志願服務時數。
And then later on the evening we'll go around again just to make sure that everybody is where they're supposed to be.
晚上稍後時間，職員還會來回巡視，確保每個人都在他們該待著的地方。
At 11:00 all students are in their rooms followed by a lights out at 11:30
十一點，所有學生都應該留在自己的房間內；十一點半便會關燈。
Although the weekend schedule varies,
週末的時間表會有點變化，
here in boarding we like to keep a structured weekday routine,
但是在平日，仍然希望保持有規律的作息流程，
to allow students to focus on academics and further develop their life skills.
讓同學們專心學業和培養生活技能。